ACTWU's Murray Finley Records from the President's Office 5619/036
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Esskay MFG Company, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Export Political Action Committee- Bipartisan Coalition for Americans, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Finances, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Fair, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Father`s Day Council, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board, 1983-1985 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- The Fletcher School, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Footwear Industries of America, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- Full Employment Action Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Foreign Policy Association, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- 14th Street Union Square Area project, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Fox-Knapp MFG Company, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Freedom House, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- National Committee for Employment, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Fund for a Democratic Majority, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Footwear, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Footwear, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Footwear, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- The Fletcher School, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Footwear Press Conference, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  January 2
- Footwear, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- MHF Papers, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- MHF Papers, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Full Employment Action Council, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Full Employment Action Council- Financial Reports, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Full Employment Action Council Steering Committee, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Fund for a Democratic Majority, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Fund for New Priorities in America, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade Luncheon, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Gallup Organization, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Bob Ganz, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Charles Garrahan Dinner, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  January 24
- MeirGatt Luncheon, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- GEB Meeting, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  September 29
- Lillian Furlan, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  August 1-5
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  April 11
- Request for Dues Increase, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 31)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  January 20-21
- Requests for Dues Increase- General Executive Board Meeting, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  July 27-30
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  May 20-21
- Requests for Dues Increase, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  May 20
- General Executive Board Meeting- Puerto Rico, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  march 8
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  March 8-11
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1887 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  October 28-30
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  March 8-10
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  July 14
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1983-1986 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  January 9-10, January 19-20
- General Executive Board Meeting- Anaheim California, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  October 31-November 21
- General Executive Board- Tarrytown, New York, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  July 29- August 2
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board meeting, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  June 4-6
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  May 1-3
- General Executive Board, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- General Executive Board, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- General Executive Board, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  May 5-8
- General Executive Board Resolutions, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  October 26
- General Executive Board- Requests for Dues Increase and Assessment, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  May 25
- General Executive Board- request for dues increase, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  April 14-15
- General Executive Board- Requests for dues increases and assessments, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  April 14
- General Executive Board Meeting, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  February 25-27
- General Executive Board- requests for dues increase and assessments, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  February 23
- General Executive Board, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  January 7-8
- General Executive Board- Requests for dues increase and assessments, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  January 7
- General Officers Reports, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Geneva, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  November 20
- John Gray Dinner, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  March 23
- Greater Cincinnati Chapter of Industrial Relations Research Association, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Greetings, 1981-1983 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Greyhound Bus Lines, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Germany, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Gimbels- Milwaukee, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Greetings and Condolences, 1984-1987 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Haggar, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Hanes Corporation, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 30)
- HSM- Quality of Life, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Hart, Schaffner, and Marx, 1981-1983 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Harvard University, 1981-1984 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Harvard University, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Harvard University, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Center for International Affairs- Harvard University, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  April 25-26
- Center for International Affairs, 1983-1984 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Headwear Division, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Health and Safety Committees, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Center for International Health Insurance, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Senator John Heinz Luncheon, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  February 5
- Hickey- Freeman Company, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Sidney Hillman Health Center, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Sam Hirsch, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Hispanic Labor Committee, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Histadrut, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- ACTWU- Histadrut Institution, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  March 4
- ACTWU housing, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Hughes and Hatcher, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Kuppenheimer, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Kuppenheimer, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Frank Saltz versus Hart Schaffner, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Health and Safety Committee, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Hindman Settlement School, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Histadrut, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- General, 1983-1985 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Industrial Arms foundation, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Industrial Department, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Industrial Homework, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Industrial Policy, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Industrial Policy, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 30)
- Industrial relations Association of Chicago, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- Helsinki Accord, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- Industrial Union Department, 1982-1983 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- The Inheritance, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Institute for Internal Economics, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Institute for Labor and Mental Health, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Imports Rally, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  October 10
- International Association of Clothing Designers, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- International Association of Machinist and Aerospace Workers, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- IBEW, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- International Federation of Chemical, Energy and general Workers Union, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- International Institute for Strategic Studies, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- International Molders and Allied Workers Union, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- International Monetary Fund, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Japan, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Joint Job Training Incorporation, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- ILGWU, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- ILGWU, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- ILGWU, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- International Union of Operating Engineers, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Ireland, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- International Jewellery Workers Union, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Income Tax Revision, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Industrial Area Foundation, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Industrial Homework, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Industrial Union Department, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Industrial Union Department, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Institute for International Economics, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Institute for International Economics, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Institute for National Economic and Social Dialogue, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- International Textile, Garment, and Leather Workers` Federation, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Interamerican Textile, Leather, Garment, and Shoe Workers Federation, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 27)
- Ireland, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 28)
- Irish- American Labor Coalition, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 29)
- Israel, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 30)
- Japan, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 31)
- Justice and Peace Mobilization, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 32)
- Joint Job Training- Board of Directors Meeting, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 33)
- Joint Job Training Incorporated- Finances, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- Service and Allied Industries Joint Board- General, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 35)
- Amalgamated Cleaners and Dryers Joint Board- Retirement Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries- Retirement Fund, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries- Insurance Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated service and allied industries- Louis Simon Health Center, 1979-1984 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated service and allied industries joint board- local 324 insurance fund, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Baltimore Regional Joint board, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Chicago and central states joint board-Amalgamated social benefits association, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Chicago and central states joint board-, 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Cleveland Joint Board, 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Jewish labor Committee, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Joseph and Feiss Company, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Kellogg Graduate School of Management- Northwestern university, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Kamber Group, 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Kamber Group, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Kamber Group, 1985-1987 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Kamber Group, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Senator Edward Kennedy, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Knights of Malta, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Knitted Textile Assistance, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Korea, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- Kwasha Lipton, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Labor Day, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- John Herling`s Labor Letters, 1980-1983 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Labor Research Assistance, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Labor Today, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Labor Theater, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Application for Labor Unity Editor, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Labor Unity, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Frank Lautenberg Dinner, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Leadership on Civil Rights, 1979-1985 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Leadership Conference, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  June 10-11
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Legal Services Corporation, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Lehigh University, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Sidney Lens, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Andrew Levin, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Malcolm Lovell, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Mailgrams, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Manhattan College, 1982-1986 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Millennium Management, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- March of Dimes, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- March on Washington, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  August 27
- Maremont Company, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Mayor`s Fashion Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Mayor`s Task Force on Holocaust Memorial, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Metropolitan Housing Development Corporation, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Senator Mondale, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Senator Pat Moynihan, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Daniel P Moynihan, 1981-1984 (Box 37, Folder 29)
- National Commission for Employment Policy, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- National Conference for Quality, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 33)
- National Democratic Institute for International Affairs, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 34)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multi employer Plans, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- National Economic Recovery Project Ottinger, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- National Knitwear and Sportswear Association, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- National Labor Committee in Support of Democracy and Human Rights in El Salvador, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- National Labor Relations Act, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- National Organization of Women, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- National Policy Exchange, 1981-1982 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- National Resource Center for Consumers of Legal Services, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- National Urban League, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Neckwear, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- New School for Social Research, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Nestole Boycott, 1982-1984 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Department of Occupational Safety and Health, 1984-1986 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Occupational Safety and Health Association, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Post Hearing Statement on the Occupational Safety and Health Association Cotton Dust Standard, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  December 14
- New Direction Incorporated, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- New England Hospital Assembly, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- National research Council, 1985-1986 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- National research Council, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- The New Framework group, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- New Framework group, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- New Jersey, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- 1982 New Jersey Election (Box 38, Folder 24)
- New Jersey Labor Management Conference, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- New York Amsterdam News, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- New York City Central Labor Council, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- New York City Government, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- New York City partnership, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- New York Labor Leaders, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- New York State AFL-CIO, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 31)
- NYS Committee for National Health, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- NYS- Department of Labor, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- New York University, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- NYS School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- New York government, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Nicaragua, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Nuclear freeze, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Nuclear Freeze campaign, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Occupational Medicine Conference, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Occupational safety and Health Act, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Occupational safety and Health Act, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Occupational safety and Health Act, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Occupational safety and Health Act Demonstration, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  May 4
- Office Memos, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Scott Hoyman Report, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Organizing, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Organizing, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Carmen Papale, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Presidential Classrooms for Young Americans, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- The Public Agenda Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Pay Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Political Action Department, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Plaques, 1979-1985 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Poland, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Park Ave. MFG. Co. St. Louis, Mo., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- P.A.T.Co, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Peace Studies Institute, 1981-1985 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Pensions, 1985 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Phoenix Clothes, 1979-1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Planned Parenthood, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Plant Closings & Layoffs, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Office of Policy Development (U.S. Government), 1984-1986 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Politics, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Jacob S. Potofsky, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped, 1981 (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Proposition One, Inc., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- The Public Agenda Foundation 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Separated into two folders due to the amount of content.
- Publicity and Promotion, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Quality of Work, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Reagan Budget, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- President Reagan's Labor Committee, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Regrets/Invitations - 1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Republican National Comm., 1983-1984 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Research Department Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1979-1983 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Research Dept.-Economic Condition 1982-1983-'84, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Research Department 1985, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Research Dept.- Industry Summary & Statistics, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Research Dept.- NLRB Elections_Firm Info, 1978-1984 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Research Dept. - Surveys (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Research Institute on International Change-Colombia University, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Reunion of Old Timers, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Right to Work (Complaint), 1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  English and Spanish
- Franklin D. Roosevelt Centennial Committee, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Roosevelt University, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Sane, 1977-1981 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Scarelle Clothing Company (Penn. State Clothing) J. Fox, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- School of Advanced International Studies, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Senior Pac, 1984 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Shoe Division - 1982-1983, 1982-1985 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Louis & Irene Simon Scholarship Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Sloan Commission on Government and Higher Education, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  One Photograph
- Social Democrats, USA 1982-1983 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Social Security, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Speech Materials, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Frank Sasser & Ziggie Halpern Modern Jacket Co.- California MFG. Co St Louis, Mo., 1981-1982 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Stowe, Vermont, 1985 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- State University of New York SUNY, 1985-1986 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Henrietta A. Dabney, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- SUNY - 1985 - independent Commission (Box 43, Folder 1)
- J.P Stevens Co. Congratulatory Notes, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  2 Newspapers
- J.P Stevens, 1982-1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Mr. Finley, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- J.P Stevens - 1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- J.P Stevens 1982-1983, 1981-1984 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- J.P Stevens Special, 1981-1989 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Szold & Brandwen, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Tariff Bills, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Task Force for Democracy, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Task Force on Regulatory Relief, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Tailored Clothing Technology corp/ (Tc2) 1982-1983, 1981-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Tailored clothing Technology (Tc2) 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Tax Law, 1985-1987 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Technological Change Textile/Garment Industry (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Testimony - Textile/Apparel Imports, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Texprint, 1981-1982 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Textile/Apparel Imports, 1983-1987 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Textile/Apparel import MTG. 12/19/83 + related matters (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Textile Apparel Imports Steering Group - ATMI 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Textile & Apparel Recovery Act of 1985, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Textile Division, 1982 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Textile Industry 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Textile Week (World), 1983-1984 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- The Trilateral Commission, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Textile White Paper, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- U.N Association of the U.S.A, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- United Automobile Workers 1982=1983, 1982-1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- United Furniture Workers of America, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- United Furniture Workers 1982-1983, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- United Hebrew Trades, 1982-1986 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- United Merchants & Manufacturers, 1982-1984 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- United Methodist Church, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- United Nations - Business and Labor Economic Council, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- U.S Department of Labor, 1980-1984 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- United States Senate, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- U.S. Senate Democratic Leadership Circle, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- United Way of America, 1981-1985 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- University of Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Committee Support of Steelworkers in USX Lockout, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Wage/Price Standards, 1979 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Washington Shuttle tickets-MHF, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Western Behavioral Sciences Institute, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Western Hemisphere, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- The White House, 1978-1984 (Box 45, Folder 21)
- White House Conference on Aging, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- White House Conference on Families, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Wickes Labor-Benefit Creditors' Committee (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Workers' Compensation Board, 1983-1985 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Workers Defense League, 1981-1984 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Workmen's Circle, 1981-1985 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Yiddish National Theatre, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Youth:2000, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Zensen - ACTWU - ILGWU Third joint Conference March 16-17, 1981 Printed Materials (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Zensen - ACTWU - ILGWU Third Joint Conference March 16-17, 1981 General (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Domei/AFL-CIO Conference May 19, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Alatex, INS. Alabama: Andalusia Alabama: Enterprise # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Alatex, Incorporated Alabama: Brantley # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Alatex, Incorporated Alabama: Troy # TRA, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- California, San Diego Alan John Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- California San Diego Rather Clothes Corp., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Colorado Denver Zohn Manufacturing Co. Inc., 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Florida: Miami # TRA, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Georgia Americas Manhattan Shirt Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Georgia Ashburn Manhattan Shirt co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Georgia Jesup Manhattan Shirt Co. Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Illinois: Balesburg # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Ill. Chicago Dubow Sporting goods Division Golf Ball, Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Ill. Chicago Hart Schaffner + Marx Clothes, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Illinois Rock Island Hart Schaffer and Marx Clothes, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Indiana Columbus Roviar Sportswear Incorporated, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Indiana East Chicago Albert Given Manufacturing Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Indiana Gary Arthur Winer Inc., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- TRA Cotton Indiana Kokomo Star Glove Co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Indiana Michigan City # TRA, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Indiana New Albany M.A. Seinsheimer co., 1976 (Box 47, Folder 20)